[
  {
    "question": "6 ÷ 3 = ?",
    "correct": "2",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "1",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 ÷ 4 = ?",
    "correct": "2",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 ÷ 3 = ?",
    "correct": "3",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "4",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 ÷ 7 = ?",
    "correct": "1",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "2",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 ÷ 1 = ?",
    "correct": "5",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "6",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 ÷ 2 = ?",
    "correct": "4",
    "choices": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "3",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 ÷ 1 = ?",
    "correct": "9",
    "choices": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 ÷ 2 = ?",
    "correct": "3",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 ÷ 2 = ?",
    "correct": "2",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "1",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 ÷ 5 = ?",
    "correct": "1",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "5",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 ÷ 1 = ?",
    "correct": "4",
    "choices": [
      "4",
      "3",
      "5",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 ÷ 8 = ?",
    "correct": "1",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "2",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 ÷ 6 = ?",
    "correct": "1",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "2",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 ÷ 9 = ?",
    "correct": "1",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "3",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 ÷ 1 = ?",
    "correct": "3",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "4",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 ÷ 1 = ?",
    "correct": "7",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "5",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 ÷ 1 = ?",
    "correct": "6",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "7",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 ÷ 2 = ?",
    "correct": "1",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "0",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 ÷ 1 = ?",
    "correct": "8",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "6",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 ÷ 3 = ?",
    "correct": "1",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "2",
      "3"
    ]
  }
]
